Woon Eusean

Software Engineer

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Computer Science graduate from Asia Pacific University with a strong foundation in programming concepts. My experience in my internships and hackathons has strengthened my technical and communication skills. Currently, my strength lies within front-end and back-end development.

CONTACT DETAILS

Phone: +60129986301

Email: woon.eusean@outlook.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/wooneusean
GitHub: github.com/wooneusean

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Bachelor' Degree in Computer Science

Asia Pacific University | 2021 - 2023 3.65 / 4.00 (First Class)

Diploma in Software Engineering

Asia Pacific University | 2019 - 2021 3.90 / 4.00 (First Class)

WORK HISTORY

Application Development Intern

Touch n Go Sdn Bhd | 07/2022 - 11/2022

- Develop Java 8 Spring Boot microservices and deploy with CI/CD workflow with Jenkins.
- Use Alibaba Cloud to monitor deployed microservices.
- Used JPA and Hibernate for efficient app development.
- Worked with MySQL to store and fetch millions of rows of data with microservices.
- Utilized Apache Kafka for microservice communication.
- Utilized GitLab for version control.

Software Engineer Intern

InfinitiLab Sdn Bhd | 04/2021 - 08/2021

- Developed front-end interfaces with Angular framework.
- Developed back-end services with **ASP.NET**.
- Utilized MySQL for storing and fetching data.
- Utilized BitBucket for version control.

ACHIEVEMENTS

1st place @ Hacktitude Malaysia 2023

- Worked as a **team of 3** to surpass more than 50 university teams by producing an application that passed all tests **under 9 hours**.
- Write code to conform to tests with Node.js and Express.js

1st place @ JomHack ImpactHack 2023

- Worked as a team of 4 to surpass 100 teams of university and industry players in a 3-day timeframe.
- Used Next.js and Flask for solution of an all-in-one tool for SMEs to integrate multiple channels of data into one for better management and knowledge.
- Implemented voice recognition, ChatGPT integration, and stable diffusion for image and video generation.

1st place @ UMHackathon 2023 - Venture Capital

- Worked as a team of 4 to surpass 30 university teams under pressure and a 3-day time constraint.
- Used Next.js and Flask for solution of a web-app to assist venture capitalists with automated due diligence with help of Al recommendations and sentiment analysis.

ACTIVITIES

Open-Source Contribution @ faker-js/faker
Open-Source Contribution @ drakkan/sftpgo

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

Skill	Skill Level (0 – 10)
Java	9
C#	8
Python	7
JavaScript	9
React.js	9
HTML	9
CSS	9
MySQL	8